♪ In the not too distant future
♪ Way down in Deep 13
♪ The evil Dr. Forrester
♪ Was hatchin' a nasty scheme
♪ He hired a temp
by the name of Mike
♪ Just a regular
Joe he didn't like
♪ His experiment
needed a good test case
♪ So he conked him on the noggin
♪ And he shot him into space
Get me down.
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La la la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And I'll monitor his mind
♪ La la la
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La la la
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ Cambot
Show yourself.
♪ Gypsy
I'm not ready.
♪ Tom Servo
Hello there.
♪ Crow
That's one O.
♪ If you're wonderin'
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La la la
♪ Just repeat to
yourself it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
Did I tell you
my mother's here?
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(mechanical blips and whirs)
Hi, everyone, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
In honor of the Fall Classics,
Servo's gonna chuck
a few in here.
We're gonna play
a little hardball.
Come on, stand in there, beba.
You bet I'm gonna
stand in here, beba.
- Hey, batter, batter
- Come on
- Come on, here we go.
- batter, batter,
batter, batter, batter, swing.
Hiyreah.
(Gypsy giggles)
Hiyreah?
What do you mean hiyreah,
that ball almost hit me.
Mike, you can't argue balls
and strikes, I'll bounce ya.
What's the matter, Nelson?
Can't handle a
little chin music?
Come on, you momma's
boy, you weak
All right, come on, come.
Gimme that weak ass cheese.
Batter, batter, batter,
batter, batter, batter.
- Ow.
- Hiyreah.
All right, that's
it, that's it.
Come on, Nelson, come on.
Oh, you're gonna give it to me?
I'll give it right back to ya.
Order, order in the
court, order in the court.
(energetic 80s techno beat)
(sobs)
All right, Mike, got
your hamburger sandwich
and french fried
potatoes for ya, pal.
Oh, thanks a lot,
Servo, I appreciate that.
I'm sorry, what
was that you said?
I said thanks, okay, oh, you
(Crow giggles)
Mike, now say, "I was
born on a pirate ship."
I was born on a pirate, hey.
(Crow and Tom Servo laugh)
Okay, I'm just not good,
because I think that--
Well, why don't we get
the cans and the bottles.
And just not drink the cans.
We'll have to get the
cans and the bottles.
Hi, guys, Pearl and I
have some news for you.
Cool beans, Art,
the studio bought
one of your screenplays:
Earth versus Soup.
(gasps) You have
got to me kidding me.
Oh, no way, oh, man.
Oh, no way, oh, man, I
finally sold a screenplay.
(excited whooping)
Okay, people, the
long and short of it
is that Mother and
I are in charge.
And we'll be shepherding your
little project for the studio.
Mm-hmm, great, okay, guys.
We need to talk
about some things.
Do you have all
your people there?
Good.
Oh, do you have your scripts?
Is everyone set to go?
How was lunch?
Okay, great.
Art, I have looked
over your script.
Oh, good.
Let me just say
that I will not have this
script tampered with.
And clearly there are some
major script revisions needed.
Sure, great, absolutely.
Fine, fine, whatever.
And what kind of budget are
we lookin' at here, Pearl?
Dr. Forrester?
Well, we could only
get you about 30,000,000
for the entire movie, so
how that shakes out is
roughly, well, 10%
for each of us.
10% for the company, insurance.
Administration, holding
fee, completion bonds.
So, we should be
able to shoot you
about $800 for the entire movie.
What?
(Mike and Tom Servo laugh)
800 from 30 mil?
I can't do anything
for $800, come on.
Oh.
(sighs) Hal Needham once said,
"Give me a Firebird and
a dilapidated building
"and I'll give you drama."
(groans) 800
sounds fine. (groans)
Okay, all right, okay,
okay, we're makin' a movie.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
And you guys are
gonna be in my movie.
All right, yeah.
And the studio
insists on Kevin Bacon.
Kevin Bacon?
How are we supposed
to get Kevin Bacon?
We can't afford him.
How are we gonna
get him up here?
Well, again, guys,
this is the big time.
Well, the time has come
to look at this issue.
And by the end of the day,
we'll be glad you did.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Sure, fine, sounds good.
I'll get my people
right on that.
Oh, and Dr. Forrester, Pearl?
Thank you.
(alarm buzzes)
Okay, people.
What are we doing
standing around here?
We've got movie time.
(all shout)
(mechanical blips and whirs)
Round Guy With
Surfboard International.
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
(explosion)
Shouldn't we be
looking through a pinhole
in a piece of cardboard?
Yep, looks like we
saved Kuwait again.
Edie Sedgwick, no.
Global warming is a big ruse
by some liberal
Pablum-puking liberals.
(chuckling)
(sweeping music)
Wow, this has Rosenburg
to the max. (chuckles)
♪ Ground control to Rosenberg
30 seconds and counting.
Astronauts report,
conditions good.
Low humidity.
T minus 25 seconds.
Mets lost today.
20 seconds and counting.
The George Hamilton story.
(giggling)
Guidance, internal.
Are these guys talking to us?
12, 11, 10
Is he the guy they jam
into freeway overpasses?
(laughing)
Ignition sequence occurs.
- Six.
- And it just goes on
- Five.
- from there.
- You get the idea.
- Four.
Boy, I'm cold, burr.
Three, two, one.
(laughing)
Liftoff, we have a liftoff.
Don't we?
Come on, back me up on this,
don't we have a liftoff?
Saturn, clear.
Boy, they got to Saturn fast.
Well it's all freeways now.
(Crow vocalizes wonder)
You just zip right there.
Used to be all torn up.
Scorpio five to
Houston Control.
I just called to talk.
40 seconds.
Well, somebody better
start melting pretty soon
or I'm gonna lose patience.
I hope they have Houston
on their speed dial.
They sure call them a lot.
Control, good it one minute.
Roger.
These are so flexible,
I can pick up a dime, over.
They shouldn't
have had Phil Spector
- design their space capsule.
- Cool.
Thanks for
camping out with me.
(chuckling)
(tense music)
I thought you were gonna
turn the yard light off.
Shut down 210 by 305.6.
I still think we should
have gone to Venus.
Entering rings.
Roger, we copy.
All is confirmed.
Lose contact through
Saturn's rings.
Pick up 10, 5.8, good luck.
Thank you.
Roger, out.
Really, thank you,
you've been great.
RCS indicates green.
- Green confirmed.
- I knew that.
Oxygen meters, auto.
Now can you stir the tanks
without killing us this time?
IMU, clear to reverse.
You are not me,
quit saying that.
No one has ever seen
anything like this.
We're still on the pad, Ron.
(uneasy music)
Fakey.
The Russians, hey, Yorgi.
All communication back.
(strange distortions)
Oh, it's the confuse-ometer.
It's all the same
crap from Apollo 13.
Hey, it's us.
There we are. (chuckles)
Houston, (audio cuts out)
Steve do you (audio cuts out)
Houston? Could you turn your
radio down, please?
Steve, are you all right?
Communication's back.
I read you, I read you.
Just blow up
and melt, come on.
(giggling)
(eerie notes)
Magnificent.
You've never seen anything
until you've seen the sun
through the rings of Saturn.
(grumbling)
Yeah, that's not what this is,
but we'll show you a film
that sort of suggests it.
(explosion)
Uh, how much did
you guys like Jupiter?
I think we just blew it
up, sorry, over. (chuckles)
(tense notes)
Yeah, I suppose we
oughta get back to Saturn.
Kind of looks like
a map of Vietnam.
(chuckling)
(mumbling)
(explosion)
I just realized,
I'm LeRoy Neiman.
(goofy vocalizations)
(groans) That was
one hot burrito.
(confused vocalizations)
(curious music)
Well, let's go
to Picture Picture.
(chuckling)
You're looking live
at the parquet floor
of NASA's hospital.
I hope that's not
Rosie O'Donnell.
(plucky music)
I don't think the happy
clown therapy is helping.
(giggling)
Well, melted at
1:30 and at 4:00.
(tense music)
Let's see, recumbent
bike's available at 4:00.
(odd chimes)
(Tom Servo mumbles)
Nothing's helping.
I tried scrubbing him out.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Linda Ronstadt.
Why was he the
only one to survive?
(uneasy tones)
He looks like a bowling ball.
The printer cable came
undone. (Crow giggles)
I better call Ted Nelson.
Check his vital signs
every 15 minutes.
And replace the IV with
units of whole blood.
Not 2%.
Yes, sir, I'll
send for an orderly.
No.
Get it yourself.
It's imperative that
this be kept secret.
Yes, sir.
And I'll need a more
tight-fitting uniform.
I'll just wait here.
So, who do you
like in the game?
Hello?
Andy Pandy.
(chuckling)
They should have
taken his ski boots off
before they put him down.
(foreboding music)
Someone put the TV
on the ceiling, please.
♪ Delta Dawn, what's
that flower you have on
Well, he's got a
nice chambray shirt on.
Yeah.
Bedpan, bed, never mind.
(tense music)
Oh, I really should get up.
(groaning)
Oh, I'm in the mood
for 14 CC of Ringer's
lactate or somethin'.
(smacks lips)
(gasps) I've been jerked.
My wedding ring,
where's my wedding ring?
He's in with some kid
gettin' his tonsils out.
(giggling)
I came in for a vasectomy.
Oh, no, save the wrapping.
(jarring notes)
(gasping)
I'm a dried apple head.
You'll find me me in
a shop in Door County.
(chuckling)
Uh, Melt, you got a
little somethin' (mumbles).
Marshmallows, I
hate marshmallows.
Keith Moon in the hospital.
(chuckling)
(nurse screams)
(glass shatters)
(Crow vocalizes disgust)
Oh, come on, I need
reassurance right now.
I'm feeling kind of vulnerable.
(eerie notes)
That's some weak
Kool-Aid, huh?
(blood curdling scream)
Why is she running through
the E-Z Mini Storage?
(screaming)
We can repair her.
She'll be better,
faster, stronger.
(Tom Servo and Crow bark)
No, no.
(nurse screams and cries out)
I suppose this is where
they keep all the parts then.
Come to Organ Donor City.
We'll help you find the organ
that's just right for you.
(screaming)
She's a tad
squeamish for a nurse.
Ya think?
No, I'll get the
door, thank you.
My dress is too small.
Oh, (groans) that's
doubly painful, ow.
(laughing)
He's on Rollerblades.
(nurse screams)
I'm not gonna look
silly in this shot, am I?
I will maintain my dignity?
(nurse screams)
(siren wails)
(Tom Servo hums)
This week on Emergency!:
patient drop-off.
(giggling)
Well, doctor, shall
we uncover the buffet?
All right, what have you got?
Over here.
What have we got?
We've got a lot.
We've got a team that's red hot.
Why don't I just
weigh my salad,
and then we'll
start the autopsy.
(unsettling music)
I pulled her wisdom teeth out
through her skull.
So what do you think?
I told her not to
pick at that thing.
Don't quote me.
But this wasn't any animal.
I had misidentified
her as an elk.
(chuckling)
And that's not all.
- It gets worse.
- We couldn't get a tee time.
I'm speaking to you
from the fallopian tube.
(low clicking)
Great.
She's full of crickets.
Well, it's not
enough to harm us, Ted.
But the radiation is
not our real problem.
We don't even know whether
it's contagious or not.
I can't believe
you said that to me.
That really hurt.
Dr. Mod, and Dr. Groovy.
(Tom Servo imitates funky beat)
He shouldn't have escaped.
They're not gonna
like this, Ted.
That's Eight O'Clock Coffee,
It's all we had, sorry.
Boy, the hectic pace
of a doctor's life, huh?
I like the haphazard
array of medical tools.
(laughing)
I still don't believe it.
Uh, don't you think
- you better
- Lick me?
call General Perry?
(energetic 80s techno beat)
Burger King command center.
If we shift half a
million French fries
to Dallas.
(buzzing)
General Perry.
- General Perry.
- He's not here.
- Ted Nelson.
- Hello.
I don't know.
Maybe a thousand Whoppers
this morning, but, uh...
How are you, doctor?
Not too good.
There's a black
guy in my office.
Something's come up, General.
What do you mean?
It's about Steve.
He escaped.
(tense tones)
You wanna talk to Ma Frickert?
How long ago?
About three and
a half hours ago.
Who knows about it.
Just me and half a nurse.
Dr. Loring and myself.
(tense tones)
All right, you
keep it that way.
General, I just told you--
Doctor, you listen to me.
We've got to find him.
We've got to get him
back and re-confine him
before he hurts someone.
Are you done interrupting?
He already has.
He killed one of
our nurses, General.
Oh, my God.
General, he was
stronger than the others.
That's why he lasted so long.
Can I use the phone? (mumbles)
I don't know why, General,
but he seems to be getting
stronger all the time.
Hey, how do I get
this floppy out?
Come up with some answers.
We've got to know, we've got
to know exactly what happened
before we start to,
Oh, wait, he just came in.
before tomorrow morning.
You want it when?
I know that, General.
Then get out
there and find him.
General, I will.
Right away.
Ah, the oyster and
grapefruit breakfast.
(tense music)
(groans) Look at the gunk.
What is that, skin in those
little holes? (groans)
He hung up on me.
Let's go put dog
poop on his porch.
(mumbles) Street, 5th Street.
Oh, he's been to
a movie theater.
(chuckling)
Hence the goo.
40, 42.
He's talking to
himself like grandma.
(laughing)
♪ Then you're uptown
Dean Martin.
(chuckling)
Is he fishin' for sewer rats?
(heavy breathing)
(grumbles) Got another
condom, cigarette.
Oh, there's a body over there.
(ominous music)
(muttered singing)
(Tom Servo hums along)
Jesus is coming in
his magic spaceship.
Remember? (yells)
Already came,
the dogs are on me.
Calumet Harbor means
two things to these guys:
stunted bullheads and
Old Milwaukee beer.
(mumbles loudly)
Saint Peter. (mumbles)
Who's that?
Anybody in there?
Come on out.
Randy Johnson. (yells)
(heavy breathing)
Join me, Luke.
Who's in have there?
Oh, it's Bill Gates.
Hey, you're gonna
scare the fish.
I think the fish
can handle it.
(chuckling)
Who's back there?
I like his Moon Boots.
Come on out.
Have you tried Windows 95 yet?
(heavy breathing)
You playing some kind of game?
Or are you a melting man
who's gonna eat my face?
(laughing)
Hey, you got protoplasm
in my peanut butter.
Judy's pregnant again.
Hey, that's great.
Isn't it?
- Yeah, great, thanks.
- Yeah, I'm so happy.
It's our 3rd try, you know.
If she messes it up
this time, she's gone.
Sure hope this business
doesn't screw things up.
How many weeks is she?
14.
A little young to be
pregnant, isn't she?
She lost the other two
about this same time.
Are we moving, or
is it the building?
This'll be all she'll need.
I suppose you'll
have to tell her, huh?
That she's pregnant?
Yeah.
Well, I'm not very good
about keeping secrets from her.
Anyway, Steve was
a friend of ours.
Poor guy.
He must be going
through hell now.
So, when do you think
the people who work
here are coming back?
I don't know.
How far is your locker?
Remember now, his mind
is so completely decomposed
that by now there'll
be no rational mood.
I'm not getting anything here.
Just an occasional
flash, but no pattern.
He's gonna need human
cells to live on.
His instinct will
tel him to kill.
That's why he
killed the nurse.
No, that was a freebie.
That's about it.
Hit the water on the
right side of the green.
There's your Windows 95.
Take care of things for me.
You got it, Ace.
Sure, Ted, don't worry.
Have a good trip.
You know, whenever
anybody says to me,
"Don't worry," that's
when I start to worry.
Well, I wouldn't
worry about it.
Dad's kind of into ham radio.
NASA's a sucker for any
very-large-array salesmen.
(giggling)
These 70 small dishes
attach to any house,
allowing for
excellent reception.
Employees of Paragon Cable,
please welcome the president
of the United States.
(Tom Servo imitates fanfare)
Morning, Sweetums.
Oh, I guess I'll drive then.
I should never
have done that stint
on Mork and Mindy.
(sighing)
Driver, what's
it like up there?
(phone rings)
I'll see if I should swing by,
pick up some Durkees.
Hello.
Dr. Nelson, this is Perry.
Do you have any news for me?
Not yet, I just got in.
I had to make soup.
You're lucky you caught me.
Well, I'm coming
down there, doctor.
I'll be leaving within the hour.
I'm flying a civil jet,
I want you to meet me.
This is so bogus
that I have to work.
So, what time are
you gonna get here?
Are you bringing Brice?
About 1600 hours.
And I hope to hell
you've found him by then.
1600 hours, so like
five months from now?
Goodbye.
Should I have said goodbye?
Damnit, autch-ka.
Autch-ka, of course.
(woman's speaking
drowned out by laughter)
Sweetheart, I didn't
hear you come in.
Bastard hung up on me for
the second time today.
Karen and Richard
Carpenter at home.
I'll take that, that was
General Perry on the phone.
- Here, let me.
- At least, it was
- until he hung up on me.
- Why don't you
just sit down and relax.
I'll get your lunch.
So, how's your body coming?
I had my breasts lowered
and my hips pulled
out at odd angles.
I hope that's okay.
Her area dominates
her front side.
(chuckling)
General wants me to go
find the autch-ka melting man.
Steve escaped.
- Oh, God.
- Autch-ka?
What are you gonna do?
Well, first I've gotta
lose a little weight.
(chuckling)
Oh, did you get some crackers?
I told you yesterday that
we needed some crackers.
Oh, I forgot.
I knew there was something.
Autch-ka.
You know, there's a pad
right by the phone, you know.
You could write it down too.
You know, they made a mistake
and they just went
home with the actors.
(giggling)
So, we don't
have any crackers?
Ted, Steve.
Raging Bull.
- Steve?
- Steve had crackers.
I've gotta go
out and find Steve.
Why you?
Because nobody else
is supposed to know.
RyKrisp, Sociables, anything?
So please, don't
forget that fact
when the general gets here.
That's all I'd need
How are you gonna find him?
I can use the Geiger counter.
I can follow his trail with it.
Geiger counter?
You mean he's radioactive?
Just a little bit.
Just a little?
How long have I been
40 years older than you?
Tinker Bell, come
down out of that tree.
(unsettling music)
♪ Way down upon
the Swanee River
Ow, oh, ouch.
Where are my glasses?
I can't see a thing.
Oh boy, stuck in
a headwind here.
(chuckling)
That is one light
head, by the way.
(Crow imitates snoring)
He's off the ramp. (giggling)
Oh, and he's burstin'
with flavor too.
♪ From the land of
blood-red water
(tense music)
On the bright side,
at least I didn't break my back.
(laughing)
♪ La-la la-la la-la la-la
Joe Camel says we should.
(kid coughs)
It's alive with pleasure.
Come on, it's my turn.
It's smooth. (coughs)
I just can't see us
ever regretting this.
See, I don't cough.
You don't inhale, that's
why you don't cough.
Anyway, let's get
cracking on that script.
Well, look at what I see.
Nosey.
I won't tell.
I'm no tattletale.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Wanna play doctor?
- No.
- Architect?
Wanna play hide and seek?
Yeah, if you let me try it.
Well, that's sputtered out.
She's gonna get
lipstick on it.
(girl coughs)
It's evil.
- See.
- Sue.
(girl coughs)
It's awful.
(coughing)
Don't insult my cigarettes.
I'll never kiss
her, she smokes.
Come on, let's play
down by the waterfall.
Come on.
Yeah, maybe we'll find
Conrad Janis's skull.
(plucky lighthearted music)
♪ We're free and it's fun
♪ And we're innocent
and it'll be sad
♪ When we find a head
(Crow imitates music)
♪ There's a rhythm
going on underground
- Hey, wait a minute.
- I need a cigarette.
This used to be our fort.
(chuckling)
Okay.
But some big kids
knocked it down.
That's too bad.
Come on, let's go.
Women are so good at empathy.
(tense music)
(mechanical blips and whirs)
(soft singing)
Okay, listen up, everyone.
Our film execs, Pearl and Clay,
thought it might be a good
idea to use a small 45%
of the budget to take a
shuttle craft up here,
and have a little script confab.
It's a one page script,
can't be handle it by phone?
Button it, meat puppet.
Or I'll make sure you
can't even get a job in TV
when this is over.
Pull the middle out
of those bagels.
Ah, they're here.
Clay, Pearl, welcome.
Uh-huh, sure, whatever.
(Tom Servo chuckles)
Okay, we've got a busy day,
what have you got for us?
Well, to start, why
don't we just grab a seat.
Then I'll just nip off
for some Pellegrinos.
(Pearl groans)
Hi, how was the,
you have a good flight up here?
- Introduce me.
- Oh, right.
Clay, Pearl, have
you met Tom Servo?
No, let's go.
Okay, great.
Start with page one A,
with the script changes.
I don't have one
A, I just have one.
Did you guys fax us the changes?
Yes, ma'am, shot
those off awhile ago.
- Because this is
- I don't
- have that.
- the February 11th.
The February 11th?
Then you must Peter Grace at
the University of Minnesota.
Yeah, you don't, neither
one of these are any good.
Let's give them copies
of the March 15th.
You need the last three pages.
Yeah, the March
15th or the March 8th.
So, if you just wanna
take that one there.
All right, and also we did
that March 8th meeting.
Only the 2nd page of that one.
Not the first
page, only the 2nd.
No, because we have that one.
You have that one?
No, I don't think
you have that one.
And then
No, that's right.
Okay, all right.
Put that behind
the other ones, okay.
I don't have any.
And that should pretty much,
(loud beeping)
that should take care of it.
So, let's get started.
Okay, people, we've got
a screening to get to.
Great meeting, I really
think we're getting there.
- Uh, yeah, great.
- Wait, wait.
We got commercial signed.
We'll call you.
Okay.
Great meeting, huh? (chuckles)
(energetic 80s techno beat)
(unsettling music)
Come on out, I don't
wanna play anymore.
She's deep in left
field at Wrigley.
♪ We're gonna zoom
zoom zoom-a zoom
What, look back?
Mom, I don't wanna be
in Dad's movie anymore.
Seve Ballasteros is
way off the fairway.
I heard you.
You're behind that tree.
Now, come on out.
You have to come
out, it's not fair.
I'm tryin' to kill ya.
There are no rules per say.
(screaming)
Please, honey,
don't do that, no.
Okay, we're gonna
try that again.
You need to scream
right away, Susan.
Oh, like you're a total fox.
My radial keratotomy
surgery went haywire.
Steve, do you read me.
You dirty rat, you
killed my brother.
Am I it now?
Help me! Help me!
Hey, no screaming unless
melting men are after you.
(girl screams)
(boys laugh)
(grumbles) Nice.
Very funny article
in Swank or what?
It was probably
very hard to love kids
back in the 70s.
Mommy, help,
help, mommy, help.
It's Frankenstein.
No, Frankenstein wasn't
the actual monster,
he was the doctor.
(groans) Got hit right
in the bread basket there.
Hey, hey, honey.
We will return
to denim theater.
What's wrong, honey?
There's a Frankenstein
in the woods.
I'm not coming back,
Jim. (fakes laugh)
♪ What a day this has been,
what a rare mood I'm in
But I saw him, he's real.
(clicking)
Mr. Dung Beetle.
You saw what happened,
care to comment?
Steve, it's Ted.
Oh, that'll bring him in.
Let me help you.
(uneasy music)
Nope, nope, not over
there, whoa, whoa.
There'll be no more of those
scary horror movies for you.
No wonder you're seeing things.
There is no such
thing as Frankenstein.
It's a story, like Snow White.
Can you hear me, Steve?
I'm all alone.
I want to help you.
I want to share my
secrets with you, Steve.
Just call.
Doesn't anybody wanna
sing karaoke with me?
Steve, I want to help you.
You can't survive
out here by yourself.
They shrunk me and I'm
trapped on this huge log.
Come on back to
the hospital, Steve.
They have Jell-O today, Steve.
You can help others.
We've got to find out
what went wrong, Steve.
Billy Jack at Los Alamos.
(clicking)
There must be some
crinkly foil somewhere.
Steve, I found some
lovely wild fennel.
Oh, no.
I never wanted
to see his scat.
(emotional music)
This would be
going so much better
if he'd eaten some crackers.
(chuckling)
I'm actually beginning
to hate Hans Geiger.
(Mike vocalizes disgust)
Keep the wrist straight.
Easy, big fella, easy.
Say, there's a school
of croppies in there.
Maybe if we're lucky
he'll get gored by
a radioactive elk.
(Mike imitates urinating)
Steve.
(Geiger counter clicks)
You're overloading
my Detectron.
Steve, it's me, Ted Nelson.
Of Ted Nelson
Plumbing and Heating.
Steve, I wanna help you.
(tense tones)
Okay, fine, it's
getting to the point
where I don't wanna help you.
I just, let me, I gotta
squeeze through here.
(tense note)
Ted Nelson.
(tense notes sound twice)
Nelson, Nelson.
(tense note)
Nelson.
(series of tense notes as Tom
Servo repeats Nelson to beat)
Ted 'Crazy Legs' Nelson.
Remember I put the condom
on Mr. Carter's desk?
Now he's got the metronome
turned up way too fast.
(unsettling tones)
Oh God, Mrs. Robinson, no, no.
The chestnut blight
is bad this year.
I think that fell
off a Chianti bottle.
Oh God, It's his ear.
I've been following van Gogh.
(chuckling)
The Beatles. (cheers)
Oh, nobody here.
Ten-hut, you maggots,
where the hell are you?
It's Yosemite Sam.
The rootin'est tootin'est
shootin'est varmint.
(horn honks)
I take you to Nagril, man.
$50 US, no problem.
They're using that big
pen to indicate scale.
- Doctor.
- General.
Did anything happen?
I thought I had
him, but I lost him.
And we're outta crackers.
Well, I don't think Mr.
Malloy can change clothes.
We may have a lot
of hunting to do.
All right.
(tires squeal)
Disc brake, sorry.
(laughing)
That'll be cut, right?
My golf clubs.
(uneasy music)
(Tom Servo hums along to tune)
♪ Ted Nelson
♪ Ted Nelson, Nelson
Could you keep it on
the road, Ted Nelson.
I don't like
the looks of that.
Roving bands of coroners.
Better check it out.
Right, let's go.
Perhaps we can
improve its looks.
Wasn't it back the other way?
(trio mumbles and grumbles)
Ah, forget it.
Yeah, let's not check
it out, you're right.
I suppose it's an emergency.
(groans apathetically)
This is my pole.
No, it's my pole. (hisses)
(muffled radio chatter)
Cat Stevens is on the scene.
Not now, Gary.
We now return to Enos.
Great shot.
The general has
something to tell you.
Go ahead, General, tell him
how you don't like
the looks of this.
Hiya, Doc.
Neil.
Well, I'd rather
stand if you don't mind.
(chuckling)
Anything I can do for you?
You could paint
my house. (chuckles)
No, there's nothin'
anybody can do for him.
Just cover up the
naughty bits here.
Oh.
You've met Lydia.
Neil, this is Michael Perry.
He's visiting
- the research center.
- Ma'am.
As a friend.
Neil Blake,
pleased to meet ya.
- Sheriff.
- Ribbit.
(giggling)
- Oh, Neil, would you mind if I
- Called you some time?
took a look at the body?
No, Doc, as a matter of fact,
you may be able to tell us
what in blazes
happened to the guy.
I've been the sheriff
most of this movie,
and I never seen
anything like it.
♪ Tell me where do the
children play-ee-ay-ee-ay-ee
(laughing)
- Beat it.
- Nice sweater though.
(ominous music)
(scoffs) Yeah, had his
lawnmower up on blocks
to repair it, poor dope.
Oh, man, he likes me, d'oh.
Oh, my stars.
(gasps) Carlo Gambino.
Well, all tucked
in then, good.
Okay.
(grumbles) Get this
scumbag outta here.
(uneasy notes)
Wife's preggers, no
crackers, now this.
Well, Doc, thought
you'd be interested.
It's not good.
I'm not sayin' I'm gonna buy it.
It looks to me like that
it was done by, you know,
like a wild animal.
You know, like a bear.
No bears around
here anymore, Doc.
You know that.
Well, maybe an emperor limpet.
Yeah.
Wouldn't happen to know
anything about this case,
would you?
Nope.
That's what I thought.
Take care.
Is he playing a high school kid
or an eminent physician?
Let's get him outta here.
(tense music)
(Tom Servo hums along)
(mumbling and grumbling)
Come on, okay.
That's it, lick
your grill, come on.
Throw your wipers back,
show me a little more tire.
(laughing)
(energetic 80s techno beat)
(sweeping music)
Scorpio five from
Houston Control.
Good at one minute.
Roger.
Who reminisces
about countdowns?
It's mellow
countdowns of the 70s.
by 305.6, entering rings.
I am a fugitive
from the pajama game.
All is confirmed.
I'm just not up to running
this morning. (groans)
lose contact through
Saturn's rings.
Pick up 10, 5.8.
Customer needs
assistance in Housewares.
♪ Only love, only love
♪ Of all the dreams
you treasure
Whoa.
Steve, do you read me?
I just had the weirdest dream.
Communication's back.
I read you, I read you.
Good, this scene again.
Magnificent, you've
never seen anything
until you've seen the sun
through the rings of Saturn.
Well, now that
they show it again,
I can really see what
they were getting at.
Yeah.
(tense music)
(explosion)
Caution, filling is hot.
Had these been actual pictures
of the rings of Saturn...
I'm glad my mom bought
me this snow suit.
There's a hellfire
and brimstone watch
for Steele, Mille Lacs,
and Goodhue counties.
This makes me
thirsty for a Corona.
(laughing)
(explosion)
(groaning and coughing)
Houston, put Mr. Woodman on.
Kotter has a nosebleed.
(choking)
Wow, that went
down the wrong pipe.
(curious music)
(gasps) It's the Brute Man.
What's the matter,
don't you like it?
(chuckling)
I wish everyone would rake
so it wouldn't
stick to everything.
Half the fun of having stumps
is red goo shoes.
Sorry.
Wow, his pen blew up again.
(goofy vocalizations)
I'm losin' it, look out.
Okay, okay, it's cool.
I'm leavin', no hassle, man.
I'm movin' back on.
He needs a mission statement.
(Mike howls)
(phone rings)
Oh, recess.
Now, how do we convey the fact
that a phone is ringing?
(phone rings)
Hello.
- Hi, it's me.
- You get any crackers yet?
Are you all right?
I swiped a MoonPie
and they caught me.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Is the general there?
Yes.
Did you find him?
You are whipped.
Just say yes or no.
No.
You done with your girlfriend?
Are you going out again?
I love you, baby,
I love you so much.
I really don't know.
Do you wish you were dead?
Just a minute and I'll ask.
Hey, you wanna eat over?
You can't, too bad, I'm sorry.
Would you both like
to come to our house
for dinner tonight?
God, no.
Not tonight.
Thanks, Ted.
All I wanna do is go
home and get some sleep.
I have to run this
place while you're gone.
So he has to
supervise himself?
I'll accept that
invitation, Doctor.
But I warn you,
I'm in a wild mood.
We'll both take a break.
Yeah, it looks like we've
lost the poor bastard anyway.
General Perry would
love to come to dinner.
Okay.
Oh, by the way, mother
and her friend Harold
are coming over too.
Jeez, this is sitcom noir.
Judy, come on,
please, not tonight.
Can't you call
them or something?
I don't think that I
could take it tonight.
I can't, they're
already on their way.
They should have
been here by now.
Oh, look, another bat.
Do you think we
oughta stop and call?
Tell 'em we're late?
Well, they aready know
we're late, don't they?
They were broad-minded to
cast aliens in this role.
(laughing)
We should stop
and buy them a
gift or something.
- A rubber novelty.
- Like what?
Oh, I don't know.
- Candy or flowers.
- Or a lemur.
Well, you know I don't
like buying flowers.
It's such a waste of money.
They die so quickly.
And Judy should not eat
candy during her pregnancy.
My mother ate candy,
I turned out fine.
I know, you wanted
the candy for yourself.
- I did not.
- The gin game.
I still think we
should call 'em.
Did someone
switch reels on us?
We'll be there
in a few minutes.
I'm taking a shortcut.
No kidding. (sarcastic laugh)
I thought this was Park Avenue.
The Incredible
Melting Grandma.
- Aw, baby.
- You're the greatest.
Not while I'm driving.
This is still better
than Mrs. Doubtfire.
(unsettling music)
Whoa, man, they
could knock a buzzard
off a garbage skull.
(quirky music)
Look, there's an orange grove.
I'm gonna squeeze one of those
and let the juice
drip down my body.
That would be a great
gift, hot oranges.
Helen.
There's a dead turtle,
let's bring that.
Those are lemons, not oranges.
Who let one?
Oh, you're no fun anymore.
Look, and besides,
lemons would be better.
I can make you a nice
lemon meringue pie.
Would you like that, darling?
She's the Cracked
magazine guy.
Well, all right,
go steal your lemons.
(woman laughs gleefully)
She looks like a Killer
Klown from Outer Space.
I'm an imp.
I'm driving, Helen.
You old fuddy duddy.
(drowned out by chuckling)
Just stop.
(groans) God, no
more of that scene.
That really gets to me. (gags)
Scorpio five.
I think it's starting
to clear up a little.
- Could you read me?
- Look harder, Simba.
Calling Scorpio five.
Steve, do you read me?
Steve, Steve, are you all right?
Shut up, stupid
water, shut up.
I think his shampoo
had the wrong pH.
(laughing)
♪ Lay me down in the tall
grass and let me do my stuff
She's got huge bird feet.
You hurry up.
Let's go down here.
(Crow imitates turkey)
You know, we could
go to jail for this.
Oh, Harold.
I love my go-go boots.
And they were
never seen again.
Cross your fingers.
The Zardon said they
would meet us here.
(chuckling)
(unsettling tones)
By the way, I just to cuddle.
Oh, isn't this romantic?
Uh-huh.
Look at that moon.
Isn't it beautiful.
Just pick your lemons
and leave, Clara Peller.
We should be quiet now, okay.
Well, I'm not the one
who's doing the talking.
(Helen shushes)
(Harold chuckles)
♪ Skyrockets in flight
♪ Afternoon delight
I just thought of something.
- What?
- Oh, wait, I forgot.
Where do we put the lemons?
Oh, here.
You just pick 'em and
toss 'em down in here.
Helen.
Harold.
What is happening?
All right.
Now, be careful, your heart.
Of course I'll be careful.
Be quiet, Harold.
All right.
- Just get busy.
- Oh, that's later, dear.
Gimme a leg up here, honey.
Oh, oh, I'm scared.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Let's hide in one
of your skin flaps.
Hurry up.
There are yards of
cable and 15 operators
required to run these people.
(barking)
An ulster hound.
Nope, not yet.
Hold onto him, okay, now.
(chuckling)
The Getaway.
(Crow imitates turkey)
Get in, (mumbles) get in.
Oh God, we forgot
our coffee discount
at Burger King.
(barking)
No bad dogs, my ass.
Maybe it was the dog who
had the hip replacement.
Oh, the old
ticker's really goin'.
And so is the
heart. (chuckles)
Are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
Why don't we stop in town
and get a nice bottle of wine.
- And drink it in the car.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
(heavy breathing)
(tense notes)
Folks, I'm with the DNR.
I'm investigating the theft of
some lemons from this grove.
Here you go, babe.
Ted, I'm worried about
my mother and Harold.
They should have
been here by now.
You know how the citrus
industry tempts them.
Well, have you tried
calling her apartment?
Yeah, every 10 minutes
for the last hour.
Well, then they
must be dead then.
Well, what about his place?
Do we have his number?
Oh, his phone's been
disconnected. (sighs)
Hey, listen, hun, I
bet I know what happened.
I bet you that old
car of his broke down.
There's got to be a
simple explanation.
So stop worrying.
He probably went off the road
and hit a bridge abutment.
I'm sorry, it's
just, I don't know.
Steve.
- My mother.
- My face.
- No crackers.
- I'm frightened.
What about Steve, Mrs. Nelson?
And why are you frightened?
Well, come on in, I guess.
General Perry, I thought
you we taking a nap.
I was, it seems that
I've awakened just in time.
I had a bad dream.
Doctor, you are a civilian.
But in this emergency,
you're in my direct command.
And I was quite
specific when I told you
that no information would
be divulged to anyone.
Come on, let's
get out of here.
Oh, for Christ's
sake, she's my wife.
That does not exclude
her from my orders.
Everybody's gonna know
about it by morning.
(energetic 80s techno beat)
(Gypsy mumbles)
We gonna shoot this
anytime today or what?
Why, Ben, you watch yourself,
you little side of priss, you.
Why, Ben, you watch yourself.
You know what, maybe Mr. Robot
will want a southern accent.
Well, I'm off, I
got things to do.
All right, hello, everyone.
Sorry, sorry.
Oh, hello, Gypsy, you
look splendid today.
Mr. Kevin Bacon, lovely to
work with you again, lovely.
Beautiful, well, well, well,
well, what are we doing.
Judy, what are we doing?
We are shooting the
film today, Mr.Robot,
and we're all set.
And the camera?
Right where it
always is, Mr. Robot.
Right over there.
- None of your lip, Judy.
- Thank you.
Ah, Cambot.
Wonderful, let's see if we can't
squeeze a little of your
magic onto 35 millimeter, hmm?
Ne sais pas?
Crow, hey, can we get goin'?
'Cause, you know,
we gotta get back
- to the movie.
- Of course.
Judy, what am I doing?
Still shooting the
first scene, Mr. Robot.
Excellent.
And action.
- Roll sound.
- Speed.
- (mumbles) the camera.
I know.
- Camera.
- Rolling.
- Marker.
- 101A, take one.
(Mike coughs)
And
action.
- Crow?
- Cut, damnit.
What is your problem, Kevin?
Well, you're
right in the shot.
I'm sorry.
(Crow grumbles)
So I am.
And suddenly you've
become the director.
Well, I guess we
can't shoot today.
Mr. Bacon isn't very happy.
Well, it just so
happens that Cassavetes
was in plenty of his own films.
And so is Stallone, Coleman
Francis, Hal Needham.
All the greats.
I know, I just
didn't think you wanted
to be smack dab
in the middle of--
Very good.
Judy, what am I doing?
We're doin' another
take, Mr. Robot.
Excellent.
And this time I choose
not to be in the scene.
Hmm, okay?
And action.
- Roll sound.
- Speed.
- Camera, camera.
I know. Camera.
- Rolling.
- Marker.
101A, take two.
And
action.
Why, Sweet Marie,
you know, I got--
Cut, print, that's
a wrap, everyone.
Beautiful work,
thank you so much.
- It's been a wonderful time.
- Wait, that's it?
That's all?
I didn't get to say beans.
We'll loop the lines in ADR.
Everything else is
second unit stuff.
Thank you, everyone, I'm off.
Bye.
Poor dope spent the whole
800 bucks on the scarf.
(alarm buzzes)
We got movie time.
We got movie time,
let's get outta here.
(mechanical blips and whirs)
(dramatic music)
Oh, boy, have I
really sunk this low?
Am I really gonna start
diggin' up bodies?
(chuckling)
Those old folks gave
him a taste for aged meat.
Ah, Benjamin gets to
the church a little late.
Churches are eager
for new members.
They'll probably just
let him right in.
I just hope he
eats the Crypt Keeper
while he's there.
God bless Drippy,
and Runny, and Sticky.
Oh, Roughy, why
did you have to die?
(fake sobs)
Oh, he forgot to take
his apricot facial off.
That's what's goin' on.
Another victim of the
great honey-dijon disaster.
Astronauts report conditions.
Oh, I should have
brought a Kleenex.
(fake sniffles)
20 seconds and counting.
Resurrection in T minus 15.
15 seconds.
Lord's main
boosters have ignited.
(laughing)
Wow.
12, 11, 10, nine.
Oh, man, I got this
flashback sequence memorized.
Ignition sequence occurs.
He shoulda had
his colors done.
Five, four, three.
It's like when
you can't get a song
- outta your head.
- Two, one.
Hey, hum Seasons in the Sun,
that should dislodge it.
Liftoff.
We have a liftoff.
Man, this flashback just sorta
peters out at the end.
Bill, pick up courtesy phone.
Hey, melt somewhere
else, you loser.
(Crow and Tom Servo chatter)
Oh, man, I can't
eat another couple.
I am so full.
(unsettling music)
Well, better get cleaned up.
I'm readin' the gospel tomorrow.
I could really use
a drink about now.
- Gimme a drink!
- Not just yet.
Another road I wanna check
out before we go back home.
That'll make two whole roads.
You know, Doctor,
I was married once.
I had a good wife.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid to go home?
- No, I'm not afraid.
- I can take her.
I'm ashamed.
I don't deserve
to be Ted Nelson.
(heavy breathing)
Wow, won that little
scanning contest,
but it cost me.
(tense music)
Dad, Tommy spilled
your wood glue
and pushed me in it.
(Tom Servo makes
goofy vocalization)
You plants are
getting way too fat.
You don't need very much
water, do you, no, you don't.
(music intensifies)
Oh, yeah, that's it, baby.
Yeah, water that spider
fern now, oh, yeah.
You know, they
specifically moved
to an outer ring
suburb to get away
from incredible melting men.
(Tom Servo imitates music)
I'm enjoying my 70s lifestyle.
Tell me when the
camera's rolling, okay?
He kiped that banner
from a Catholic church.
(chuckling)
(plucky notes)
I'm knitting
myself a new husband.
(uneasy music)
I'm glad there are no books
or magazines in this home.
There is no reason for us to
have any reading material.
This'll keep the general warm
for his next nap with us.
He's Pillsbury
cinnamon glaze man.
(goofy chuckle)
This is basically
the same story
as Frosty the Snowman.
I'd love to go in,
but I don't wanna melt
all over their carpet.
(tense music)
Which way am I facing?
(heavy breathing)
He's right,
I should have anticipated
his cracker needs.
That's an enormous bootie.
(chuckling)
Yep, Ted's lucky
to have married a
pistol like her.
Is he crying or dripping?
♪ I'll stop the world
and melt with you
(laughing)
Wow, she's knitted a
lot of pillows tonight.
Remember when everyone had
one of those giant black
velvet moth posters?
(ominous tones)
All right, well,
nothing's happenin' here.
I got stuff to do.
(distant crashing)
Ah, she dropped a stitch.
- Hence the crash.
- Ted?
Is that you?
(jarring note)
Just rubbin' my legs together.
Don't mess with
the timpani, honey.
I had it tuned for the Mahler.
(wooden knocking)
Airto, is that you?
(Tom Servo imitates tense tones)
(strange distortions)
(goofy vocalizations)
(silly vocalizations)
The melting man just
needs to borrow a kettle
to melt into.
(silly vocalizations)
Careful, the paneling
is out-acting you.
(tense tones)
Although this kitchen
is badly decorated,
it's not inherently terrifying.
You're right,
the paneling is less
wooden than her.
(goofy vocalizations)
(gasping)
Hey, I didn't do it,
I found it this way.
(sighs) Alfie.
Oh, yeah, it dragged
the milk out of the fridge
and dropped it on the floor.
Alfie. (giggles)
Look at the mess you made.
(Tom Servo giggles mockingly)
(Judy gasps)
I'm Dr. Ted Nelson.
Take it easy.
Take it easy, take it easy.
- It was Alfie.
- Take it easy.
He spilled a bottle of milk.
Take it easy.
Do I have to check you
into the sanitarium
again, honey?
(calm string melody)
Okay.
Feel better, a little bit?
Yeah.
It's like huggin' a broom.
(series of high pitched notes)
Come to Melting Man Farms
and pick your own melting man.
I didn't know your
melting man's diet
consists solely of
eucalyptus leaves.
Oh, and human flesh.
(heavy breathing)
Guess I've been behaving
like an ass lately, haven't I?
What do you in the
audience think, have I?
I don't know how to
handle these things.
- I am a doctor.
- Not a belly itcher.
I am not a policeman.
I know my mother's dead.
Rubbery trolls everywhere
mourn her passing.
(emotional music)
She's dead.
Yes, honey, we
went to the funeral
10 years ago.
I know my mother's dead.
Judy I told you that
we never found it.
I know she's dead.
Honey, Seinfeld's on.
I can feel it.
Look, darling, we're
gonna leave her out
for the polar bears anyway.
She's dead.
(groans) Don't
ask me about my day.
Oh, gee, you know, I am,
I just don't, you know, I'm, but
(distant country music)
Ah, that's what this
film needed, country music.
(chuckling)
Buford Pusser, Eating Tall.
Yeah, this is an area
that needs heavy patrolling.
(country music)
(Tom Servo hums along)
I hope she's not
using the lemons
like Susan Sarandon.
Oh, God, her hips have locked.
Ted Nelson's not here.
Ted Nelson isn't around.
Oh, man, there's
teeth and wigs
and trusses all over the
place. (disgusted vocalization)
Either they brought
a dish to pass
or that's their entrails.
(music intensifies)
Ah, yes, country music.
An ironic testament
to their tragedy.
Of course, you know,
old people are
easier to tear apart.
(chuckling)
Let's see, are we allowed
to keep road kill in this state?
You're going to
magic land, honey.
All right.
That is guaranteed
to make you sleep.
There is some gigantism
associated with this drug.
Okay, I'm gonna go out
And get some
more of this stuff.
and see the sheriff now.
But the good General Perry
is going to be here with you
the whole time, so don't worry.
Okay?
And I won't be gone long.
Any of this gettin' through?
Careful.
- I will.
- Wow, she's radiant.
Take care of yourselves.
We wills.
(uneasy music)
Bye, kid, bye.
(heavy breathing.
Hello? Movie?
Well, let's see here.
Fire, start, start, fire, fire.
General, would
you do me a favor
and stay with Judy while I
go out and meet the sheriff?
Of course, Doctor,
I'd be glad to.
There's some leftover
turkey in the refrigerator
if you'd like to have
something to eat.
That sounds good.
What about you?
You should eat
something before you go.
No, I'm not hungry.
Couldn't hold anything
down now, General.
Why don't you
just call me Mike?
- Even though my name is Trent.
- Okay.
- And I'm
- Pregnant too.
sorry about before.
About losing my composure
with you and your lady.
It's just that this whole
thing's really got me uptight.
That's all right.
Should I take
anything out to thaw?
We just weren't prepared
for anything like this.
But I did get the lead
in the Coleman Francis Story.
Nasty mess.
You can't go by the book,
there's nothing in the book.
There's no way to cope.
And there's a
clock there. (sighs)
- Just seven hours to go.
- Until Captain Kangaroo.
Can you stop it?
No way.
I don't follow you
my friend, no way.
There's a face you
have to get used to.
Be back as quickly as I can.
I'll guard the beer.
(tense tones)
I'm here for my dermabrasion
with Dr. Ted Nelson.
Hello?
Well, I suppose
I could reminisce
about my countdown again.
That would kill some time.
(unsettling music)
(Tom Servo imitates music)
Sounds like a Jew's
harp with a whammy bar.
Oh, hey, could
you guys snag me
some Diet Coke while you're out?
He's gonna steal
back his snowblower.
(confused vocalizations)
What? What?
I was just finding my light.
You want me, okay, okay.
Let's see, beer,
beer, baking soda,
brown mustard, beer.
God, I love you.
(unsettling music)
This man is a
brilliant tactician.
Beer, turkey leg, strip
down to my underwear,
and some porn, I'm all set.
(laughing)
Oh, he's soapin' his windows.
He's gone too far.
This is a very moist movie.
(imitates tasting) Unctuous.
Couldn't they just put
'ibid' up on the screen
for these.
(laughing)
Ah, yes, meanwhile,
her baby is discovering
the wonders of goofballs.
Could you turn some
of your lights off?
We're kinda gettin'
it next door.
(mumbling)
Ma'am, could I
borrow a drop cloth?
(eerie notes)
Oh, man.
Now it's hit my
sinuses. (snorts)
So is this the
incredible part?
I don't think.
What did go on here, Doc?
Well, during the Ice Age,
glaciers moved through,
oh, you mean recently.
Listen, you better tell me
what's goin' down around here
before there's nobody
left in this town.
Well, to begin with,
I'm Dr. Ted Nelson.
I can't do that,
Neil, it's classified.
For God's sake,
Doc, people are dying.
God, have I got gas.
Judy's mother, doesn't
that mean anything to you?
Of course it means
something to me.
I oughta run you in.
What for?
How about aiding and
abetting a criminal?
Oh, I wish I could
tell you, Neil.
I would would like to
be able to tell you.
Come on, Doc.
Now, I'm gonna find out
just what is going on.
And neither of us is leaving
this spot until I do.
What a knob.
That Perry character's got
something to to do with this,
doesn't he?
Yeah, I've seen plenty like
him when I was in the army.
Damnit, he's got brass
written all over him.
Listen, Ted, I got
a right to know.
Hey, there's Mike.
All these people
that have died.
They're my people,
Ted, and yours.
I don't own 'em, they
don't got my name on 'em.
If
I tell you, I want
you to promise me,
(Neil yells)
No, do you or do you
not want to know.
I wanna know.
Then you tell nobody,
not even your wife.
You know I live with mom.
(sighs) Well, can I hit you
with my flashlight?
You know I'm not married, Ted.
I know, I was just trying
to hurt your feelings.
I'll tell you
about it on the way.
Now let's go find him.
- Find who?
- I thought you knew.
This scene has been
over several times
and they just won't admit it.
(tense music)
Tomorrow, and
tomorrow, and tomorrow,
creeps at its petty
pace from day to day
until the last syllable
of recorded time.
I'll try the next
house, forget it.
I love you.
Will you be Mrs.
Turkey Leg Perry.
(grumbles) Well,
Merry Christmas.
I should call up some
of the other generals.
20, 21, 22, swallow. (gulps)
I wonder what Colin
is up to tonight.
(reflective music)
There's pudding
in the melting man
to make him moister.
Where could I hide this?
Let's see.
(strange tones)
(odd zipping)
Wow, good thing the
old lady's asleep.
(tense notes)
(creaking)
Steve.
You gimme a big kiss.
Oh, we saw that in Cape Fear.
Meanwhile, in limbo.
Houston, we have a problem.
We're so lost.
I hope you don't mind.
I just wanted to take
a quick look in at Judy
before we started the search.
- She alone?
- They're floating.
No, Perry's with her.
The fridge?
When's the baby due?
Don't talk about
our baby, Martha.
Not for some time yet.
It's your first, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I delivered a
baby once, right--
That's my house,
right over there.
Your finger smells.
Ted, the door's open.
Say uncle, say,
oh, oh, gotta go.
(dramatic music)
Oh, no, a speed bump.
Center car on general.
(car doors slam)
(grumbling)
Hey, look, it's the general.
Somebody took and left
a perfectly good general
layin' in the
middle of the road.
Judy.
Don't eat the
rest of the turkey.
(frantic music)
He'd make a pretty
good dip with taco chips.
Meanwhile, on
Martha's Vineyard.
Well, I sure had a good
time at the car wash, Fred.
That person looks a
lot like Bonnie Franklin
from a long way off.
♪ Some enchanted evening
♪ You may meet a redneck
♪ You may see a redneck
across a bingo hall
(Tom Servo hums a tune)
(giggling)
Let's go inside.
That's a good idea, babe.
Ah, Nell, Jesus, did you
leave the door open again?
You were the last
one out, not me.
I was?
Oh, don't you remember?
You went back in to check
what time the movie started.
Then you grabbed
the one-hitter.
- You're right.
- That's right.
What time did the movie start?
(vocalizes disgust) Did
you sneeze really hard
on the door handle?
What the hell is this stuff?
Did you have your
stigmata again?
I don't know.
Nell, there's somethin'
strange goin' on here.
I want you to wait
outside, I'm goin' in.
- No, I'm coming.
- Wait here.
I'll throw the
bologna out to you.
I'm gonna go listen to some ELO.
We're missin' the
beginning of Hee Haw.
What is it?
I wanted to talk about
the Jim Varney film.
(strange knocking)
(energetic 80s techno beat)
Judy, sweetheart, wake up.
I'll talk you down, honey.
What's going on?
There's nothing the matter.
You're okay, that's
all that counts.
I'm fine, if (wheezes)
you could just let go.
Steve was outside
and there was screaming
and yelling and--
Doc, come here, quick.
The general is still dead.
Everything's
gonna be just fine.
I'll be outside.
Looks like I'll have
to drug you again.
God, she's beautiful
when she sleeps.
Matt.
She's a strange cross
between Barry and
Cindy Williams.
Yeah, didn't she sit
behind the Sweathogs?
I'm starting to
get not-stoned.
Now, this scene is lit.
Hey, sorry, babe, I
forgot you were out there.
Jeez, how long does it take
to check a double-wide?
I hope no one disturbed
my back issues of Crawdaddy.
(tense music)
I'm gonna make up a
pitcher of sloe screws,
and put some Hungry-Man
dinners in the oven,
and fall asleep on the
couch until they burn.
Do pork rinds need
to be refrigerated?
(jarring note)
Well, hey, who cleaned up?
I guess he decided to
defrost, that's a good idea.
There's gotta be a
Jell-O shooter left.
From the Rhoda Morgenstern
line of clothing.
Matt?
I thought we were
gonna have beery sex.
I gotta go to Yodel Groceries.
There's a UFO hovering
over the shot, oh.
(strange tones)
Honey?
North Dallas Forty was
really good, didn't ya think?
Honey?
(eerie music)
Honey, you don't mind
if I put on Eat a Peach, do you?
I wish someone
would get killed
just so we could move on.
Bring us back to the melting.
(unsettling piano notes)
This is a little
game they play.
He jumps out of the dark all
pale and blotchy and nude
and hairy and
(vocalizes disgust)
(chuckling)
Is someone eating
the tuna wiggle?
Come on, other people
have to use the toilet.
(Nell screams)
The 8-track ate
Flirtin' with Disaster.
(frantic music)
I never liked where
this was. (grunts)
Come on, mollify him
with a Mickey's big mouth.
Whoa, almost lost
her On-Cor entrees.
There, now what's next?
The sink.
Gimme the number for 9-1-1.
(rattling)
Operator.
Are there any tickets
left for 38 Special?
This is Nell Winters.
Use your words.
(yells and cries out)
I'm surprised they still don't
have their Christmas lights up.
Where the hell is
that lemon zester?
Hang on, I'm gonna fix
you a bold head omelette.
The Kelvinator's
coming to attack her.
Huh, what does this do?
Yan can cook.
(tense note)
(Tom Servo meows)
Has she considered
just leaving?
(tense note)
(Tom Servo meows)
(floorboards creak)
My life was going
so well until now.
(tense notes)
(glass shatters)
(Nell screams)
(Tom Servo chuckles madly)
(Crow imitates wounded dog)
(tense music)
(all hum along)
Yes, you'll still be
able to play the piano.
That was weird.
Well, back to the
intruder in my house.
Oh, good, now we get to
see the rest of the place.
(Nell cries and screams)
Got milk?
Whoa, did they
have a racehorse
tied up to the wall?
Oh, great, now
the acid kicks in.
The director's niece,
ladies and gentlemen.
The director's niece.
Not one of these people
have been in their underwear.
What a ripoff.
I should send this in
to Life in These United
States. (chuckles)
Apparently deer have been
nibbling at the woodwork.
(Nell cries and screams)
God, I hate this wallpaper.
Wow.
What is it?
How's your wife?
She's okay, she
slept right through it.
What do you want?
Are these your begonias?
That thing near his hand,
do you think it
could be part of,
- The plot?
- you know.
No, I don't know.
Don't touch it.
It might be radioactive.
No, now, the poultry
industry has problems, but
I gather you haven't told
me everything, have you, Doc?
No, I haven't.
May I see your light?
Just as I suspected,
Lloyd's extra smoky.
(chuckles) Oh, God.
What is it, what's so funny?
Caroline in the City
last night. (chuckles)
It's a turkey leg.
A one-legged turkey did this?
The general was a
friend of Steve's, too.
Steve Two: Electric Boogaloo.
I guess Steve
has really had it.
Headquarters
callin' Sheriff Blake.
Sheriff, you can
use my flashlight.
Sheriff, do you read me?
Go, Nora.
Sheriff, we got a
call from Nell Winters.
She's in some sort of
trouble with some guy
that run in there
and he got mad and--
I'll get right on it.
Doc, come on, I think
we've found our boy.
(tense tones)
Here's the wind-up.
I can't just leave Judy here.
I can have a car
here in five minutes.
Come on, let's go.
♪ Come to my window
Give her a wire monkey
and see how she reacts.
(sniffs) I smell urine.
Oh, that's right.
(suspenseful tones)
Honey, where's the Cheez Whiz?
You got any beer?
- Nell.
Please, could I just
use somebody's bathroom.
Losing his arm has given
him the ability to run.
You always were a good
judge of men, Deathstalker.
You shouldn't
think we got trouble.
Look at that dude.
Ah, Sullivan's
Travels, of course.
He's got moths stuck to
him, cigarette butts, lint,
he's just pickin' up
everything along the way.
Hobo dinner again?
Don't let him hear us.
We're almost (mumbles)
And wipe off the
mouth when you're done.
The answer to whatever
happened to Jethro Tull.
(unsettling music)
Jeez, by this time,
he should be melted
down to a little stub.
God, I've never seen
a man puddle like this.
(Geiger counter clicks)
Forget it, he's not talkin'.
Come on, let's go.
Bye, lady, take care.
Let us know what happens.
♪ Trailer for sale or rent
♪ Rooms to let
(mechanical blips and whirs)
(groaning)
Hiya, Crow.
hey, what's the matter,
little Stroheim?
Oh, hi, guys.
The focus group from
the preview audience
of my Earth versus Soup
film is about to start.
I'm too nervous.
I'm goin' next door for a beer.
Okay, you just,
hey, wait, we don't
have a next door.
Let him go.
All right.
We've all just seen the
film Earth versus Soup.
How many people
didn't like the film.
Didn't like the film or
just didn't care for it,
by show of hands.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
So all, all didn't
like the film, okay.
How many people
did like the film?
They liked the film.
Cindy, you didn't like the film
and now you have your
hand about halfway up.
So maybe you liked
the film a little bit?
Would that be correct?
Okay, we'll get back to that.
Okay.
What about the film
didn't you like?
The film we just saw,
Earth versus Soup,
what was it about it you
didn't like or didn't care for?
Say, the plot or, yes, Gary.
Uh, the plot.
The plot, Gary
didn't like the plot.
How many other people
didn't like the plot?
By show of hands.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
So we all didn't like the plot.
Why, why didn't
we like the plot?
What was it about the
plot that we didn't like?
Doug, why didn't
you like the plot?
I liked the plot.
I just thought it was too short.
Ah, you thought it
was too short, okay.
What were your favorite
characters from the film?
If you had one
favorite character,
who would that character be?
In the film you just
saw, Earth versus Soup,
a favorite character
such as Mike or,
Cindy, yes?
Mike.
Cindy liked Mike.
How many other people liked
Mike, by show of hands.
One, two, three.
Okay, three people
liked Mike, all right.
How many people have an
allergic reaction to shellfish?
Allergic reaction or--
Mild reaction.
A mild reaction to shellfish.
So, Tony, would this keep you
from recommending
this film to a friend?
- Yes.
- Yes, yes, it would.
Because you don't
like shellfish.
You wouldn't wanna see
shellfish in a movie, okay.
What if the soup were a
different kind of soup?
Say, it was a chicken stock.
Or something like that.
Would you recommend
it to a friend
if it was potato soup?
Yes, okay.
Cindy, you had your hand up.
I don't like soup.
Oh, that's right, you're
the one who didn't like soup.
- What's that, Gary?
- I'd like a sandwich.
(chuckles) Gary
would like a sandwich.
(all laugh)
How many people would liked
to have seen Julia Ormond naked?
Julia, one, two, three,
four, so about half.
Half would like to see
Julia Ormond naked.
If you had a rat cage
strapped to your face
Again, guys, we've
got a lot of work to do.
We had 68% walkouts, we have
to get those numbers down.
Also, 74% of the audience
didn't like the character
of Cruella Deville, and
even though the character
wasn't in the movie, we have
to change those numbers.
Would you like to see
more crackers in the film?
The big kind of crackers or
the small oyster crackers?
- Saltines.
- Saltines?
Yes, good, excellent.
(energetic 80s techno beat)
(unsettling music)
You boys seen
anyone around here?
We've seen each
other, does that count?
We ain't seen nothin'.
Harvey Fierstein.
I'm in your head.
(mumbling)
He's gonna meet up
with Indestructible Man.
(tense music)
Ah, the melting man approaches
the giant barber shop.
I know this guy once who
put a penny on the track
and the train derailed.
Hey, you, hold
it or I'll fire.
Don't shoot him.
No Judy?
What?
How'd he get his gun back?
(gun fires)
(music intensifies)
You got me, you killed me.
Oh, wait, you didn't, I'm sorry.
Oh, he's gotta be
slipping all over himself.
In color.
A Quinn Martin production.
(laughing)
Now, these are the
giant brining tanks.
The provolone will sit
in these for four days.
Be careful on these stairs,
this is where we
pump the whey out.
Have you noticed how
not a single power plant
in not a single movie has ever
been locked or inaccessible?
(inquisitive vocalization)
While I'm here,
I'm gonna find out why my
bill was so high last month.
- He's down there.
- He's right here.
- Right here.
Right here, right
here. (whistling)
Fellas, fellas.
Where'd that son of a bitch go?
Hey, how'd he get a shotgun?
Ahead is the Alien 3 set,
to the left Robocop
and Terminator 2.
(heavy breathing)
Hey, look at the little guy.
Hey.
Well, he's meltin',
but he's wily.
Hey, stupid.
Doc, there he goes.
Come on, move, move.
I should just
move to a new town,
start a new life for myself.
In a town where melting
people are accepted.
Hey, this would make
an excellent fort.
No time.
Watch out for the
big pile of mucus.
(chuckles) He's dressed like
every high school burnout.
His parka is keeping
me really involved
in the movie.
(tense music)
I think the Western Avenue L
comes through here.
Do you guys know, is there
a credible melting man?
I don't.
And watch out, he can
do the 440 in ten seconds.
(Tom Servo and Mike
hum along mockingly)
Steve, stop.
♪ Oh yes they call
him the streak
♪ Fuzzy dice and
bongos, fuzzy dice
Das Blech.
You know, maybe if he took
his arm out of his shirt
it would help.
This all sounds like music
that was rejected
by Wonder Woman.
Melt, Melt, you in here?
Melt?
(Mike hums along to music)
Hey, Yo-Yo Ma,
give it a break.
I'll go hide out
in the burn unit
until this blows over.
The gooeyness of the
long distance runner.
♪ Ted Nelson, Ted Nelson, Ted
Hey.
It's incredible.
He seems to be getting
stronger as he melts.
There's your title.
We've gotta get him.
I've got to find out why.
We need to back-fill
the justification.
Here, take this, take it.
You go up that way.
I am not the NRA.
He picks up a spare.
Hey, look at this booger
that just shot outta me.
(chuckling)
- What is this stuff?
- I don't know.
Oh, I'll clean that up.
That's mine, sorry about that.
The Incredible Melting Man.
He's increda-meltable.
I haven't been
this agile in years.
I should try skiing.
(tense notes)
♪ Nelson, Nelson, Ted Nelson
Hey, what's this
spot on my sleeve?
I'm bleeding.
They turned
Barefoot in the Park
into an action movie.
♪ Nelson, Nelson, Nelson
♪ Ted, Ted Nelson, Nelson
♪ Ted Nelson, Ted Nelson
The movie comes
into sharp focus
whenever Ted Nelson
is on the screen.
Your melting was
completely cosmetic
and it wasn't covered
by your medical plan.
Wow, I should have
melted years ago.
I've never been in
better shape, look at me.
(gasps) It's pretty up here.
Must remain dull.
Oh, my god.
Steve.
My advice, never
scrimp on a rice steamer.
Okay, okay, hold
it right there.
Drop your slime.
Come on, it'd be
like shooting Jell-O.
Doc.
Do not emote.
(confused vocalizations)
Doc, what do we do now?
Well, if we put
throw-up powder on him,
he'll probably disappear.
(Steve groans)
No, Neil, no.
(laughing)
No, Neil.
Don't, stop.
Steve, please, no more.
Let him go, Steve.
Steve, my God, stop,
you're hurting him.
Steve, no.
Maybe there was a
writer in his contract
that he'd be in the film,
but he wouldn't act.
(groans of struggle)
Steve, stop.
(Neil yells in fear)
(electric zapping)
Oh, Karl Wallenda
has burst into flames.
Wow, boy, great
fireworks this year, huh?
Oh, why did I go on that
high phosphorous diet.
(electric sizzling)
(groans) I'm okay.
I just got the wind
knocked outta me.
You know, immolation is the
sincerest form of flattery.
(chuckles) Sorry.
Sorry, I thought
we were playing.
Oh, yeah, it plays much
better with these guys.
These guys are doin' better.
Dorf, security guard.
Boy, the sheriff is like
an underground tire fire.
(Tom Servo imitates sizzling)
Must have been dry,
he's really goin' up.
(coughing)
No, no, God, no.
He was my ride back.
(chuckling)
Oh, God.
He was a very close vague
acquaintance of mine.
Steve.
Hi, Ted.
What can I do ya for, Ted?
Steve, it's me, Ted.
From the trailer
cart, you know.
Steve, I wanna help you.
(Ted cries out)
Is that a yes or a no?
Steve.
One of us must be Steve.
Help me.
The stunt guys can't
hold me up any longer.
It's Ted Nelson, Steve.
It's me, Steve.
Please, it's Ted Nelson.
We were gonna open an
exotic candle store together.
Help, Steve, Steve.
These two tested well
with big, lonely white guys.
Steve, help me, please.
What's goin' on up there?
Help me.
Grab a nose hole and pull.
Steve, I can't hang on.
Steve, help me.
Please, Steve, help me.
(energetic 80s techno beat)
Please, help me.
Okay, now, when
you grab my wrist
a lot of meat is gonna
slide off, so be careful.
Oh, good, you're
not gonna pull me up
and just pop me in
your mouth, are ya?
All right.
Go ahead, just use
my ribs like a ladder
and pull yourself up.
Steve, please.
Steve.
Steve, steve.
Stop or I'll fire.
Oh, now what.
No, don't.
♪ Da-da-don't,
da-da-da-da-don't
Who the hell are you?
I'm Dr. Ted Nelson.
(Tom Servo imitates gun firing)
Don't move.
Listen to me,
I'm Dr. Ted Nelson.
(gun fires)
Wasn't far off.
Whoa, hey, no
relation to Ted Nelson.
Nope, nope.
(heavy breathing)
(gun fires)
Okay, you're not just
firing at Dr. Ted Nelson now.
(gun fires multiple times)
You're ruining my
shirt, this is a J. Crew.
(tense music)
(screaming)
So, it was all a dream.
(groans and grumbles)
I really tucked into that
security guard, I am stuffed.
Boy, that thing they
say about cellular phones?
It's true.
I wonder if this is gonna
affect his Veteran's Benefits.
Oh, solvent, my
favorite beverage.
(emotional music)
(can crashes)
(Steve cries out)
If I could just fart, I
would feel so much better.
(Steve groans loudly)
Somebody's gonna throw
him in a hockey rink.
(Steve groans grotesquely)
Ew, whoa.
Me? I'm soaking in me.
(gulping)
Man, it would really hurt
to splash on Sea
Breeze right now.
Yet he still sees 20/20.
I'm melting.
But you knew that.
It's best to just
let the Ebola virus
run its course.
(grumbles of agreement)
You know, he may
not recover from this.
This is why gentlemen
should always carry a hankie.
Maybe if I could
just keep down
some saltines and ginger ale.
Ew, he just threw himself up.
(disgusted vocalizations)
Well, his irritable
bowel syndrome
is really acting up today.
(bells chime)
In a moment the
results of that trial.
Dawn in the Serengeti.
What could there
possibly be to wrap up?
Everybody's dead.
(chuckling)
Well, the movie has to
mop up after itself now.
I guess.
(strange notes)
Ted Nelson was found
alive, and of normal size.
There was no Melting Man.
This is so ironic.
'Cause remember how
he hated metal stairs?
That's right.
(tense eerie tones)
He was pitchin' guards last
night and won three bucks.
Okay.
And let's check back in
on our Dr. Ted Nelson.
Still dead.
This is what it looks
like behind Chili's.
♪ Zip-a-dee-doo-dah,
zip-a-dee-ay
The scope of this achievement
in the never ending challenge
of space exploration.
It's the Cat in
the Hat factory.
Please remember the
last flight into space.
When astronaut Steve West
I have been to the
proletariat zones.
and Michael
Wells paved the way
I'm Garrison Keillor
with The Writer's Almanac,
stay well, do good
work, and don't melt.
they cannot be here today,
amidst all the
excitement and joy.
So he was tomato based then.
They are still under
observation at a Mobile
I hate it when dogs explode.
under the supervision
of Dr. Theodore Nelson.
However, they have
sent a telegram
Jeez, now I gotta
hose Buzz Aldrin
or somebody off
the building here.
Good hunting.
I never understood
white people.
The moments are
closing in now.
We shall hear the countdown
directly from Houston Control.
This is what happens
when you give a young
makeup artist a free hand.
Astronauts report, feels good.
T minus 25 seconds.
Well, better go
get into the capsule.
20 seconds and counting.
I've never seen
anybody throw out
that much manicotti at once.
Guidance, internal.
Okay, all set for the rodeo.
12, 11, 10,
So how many monster movies
end with a janitor scooping
a monster into a garbage can?
six, five, four,
three, two, one.
(loud booming)
Blooming space program
with loud report.
Light and get away.
Koyaanisqatsi.
Cape Kennedy was
renamed Cape Ted Nelson,
and quickly renamed
Cape Kennedy again.
(ponderous vocalizations)
- So, they learned nothing.
- Yep.
Well, I learned
somethin', Mike.
I learned doctors don't care.
I learned that
southern California
Can get cold enough
for a snorkel jacket.
Never knew that.
I learned never to
name a child Burr.
Mike, I've written
a short sketch
about Burr DeBenning.
(clears throat) Hi,
what's your name?
Burr.
Oh, here, take my coat.
Now, what's your name?
Burr. (laughs)
- Very good.
- Kill me.
Well, I also learned
never to scream, "I'm Ted
Nelson" to a security guard.
I've learned that
half eaten turkey legs
make very tepid
ironic statements.
We learned it's good
to have Saltines
around your house.
I learned that sheriffs
are full of pyrotechnics.
Jonathan Demme?
Ah, who cares, anyway.
And once again,
we learned that NASA
is staffed by two or
three people, tops.
And they hire civilian doctors
to head up the recovery program.
Yep.
What else, what else.
Oh, I learned that some nurses
can't find properly
fitting uniforms.
Mm-hmm.
I must have learned
somthin' else.
Oh, we learned that some cats
can open the refrigerator,
get the milk, bring the milk
into the middle on the kitchen,
throw it up in the air,
drop it on the floor,
shatter it all over the place.
That's a good
lesson, important.
Well, we also learned that
if you're a melting man,
you can have a short but
highly succesful career
as a sprinter.
Me, I learned that I should
never marry a passive, immobile
doctor named Ted Nelson,
who doesn't ever do anything.
And I certainly
shouldn't have his baby.
I think that's very sound.
How 'bout you?
Oh, you know what,
I learned that I could
use the word autch-ka
as an expletive if necessary.
- Autch-ka.
- Indeed, nice.
I learned that if you're gonna
have a general over for dinner,
you better have turkey
legs and beer on hand.
(chuckling)
Well, we learned that
lights and lighting
aren't really necessary
to make a film these days.
And neither are actors.
True, true.
Well, I think I learned that
I shouldn't go to Saturn
unless I have the
proper protective gear.
Yep, yep.
Yep, and right now, I'm learning
that even though this movie
is about 80 minutes long,
it feels like Berlin
Alexanderplatz.
Yep, yep.
I also learned
that some sheriffs
aren't married.
Did you know that?
- Yeah.
- I didn't.
I learned it was impossible
to look good in the 70s.
I learned that even if you
chop a monster's arm off,
it'll only make him
stronger and more powerful.
Yep, and I
learned that you can
just fill in crucial
elements of the plot
wherever it's convenient.
I did not know that.
No, did not.
We've learned that
if you're put in charge
or an urgent, top-secret
government project,
it really doesn't matter
if you do anything.
Yep, yep.
And we learned that sometimes
people can abuse
spirit gum and latex.
Oh, I hear ya.
(mechanical blips and whirs)
(Crow chitters nervously)
Well, Crow, this is it.
This is the day you find
out if Earth versus Soup,
the project that has
dominated your life for,
- Years.
- well, years, really,
gets green-lighted for release.
You nervous?
(Crow groans)
Hello? Crow?
(Crow screams abruptly)
Yeah, just get it.
Hi, guys, everybody here?
Good, good news, people.
Clayton, do you wanna tell them?
Well, the studio's
real excited
and your movie's
going to be released.
Oh, wow.
- That's excellent.
- Well, when's the premiere?
(all chatter excitedly)
As a trailer.
(Crow vocalized shock)
My movie's gonna be a trailer?
Uh-huh, this is very exciting.
This is good news.
We thought this would give
the widest possible release.
And it will help us reign
in that marketing budget.
Well, we still have
a lot of work to do.
Oh, and there's on thing
that we want to ask,
and this is going to be
covered in that $800,
is could you remove your
name from the credits
as the film's director?
Again, this is
good news, guys.
Uh, just a minute.
Let me get this straight.
I come to you with a movie.
You supposedly get me
$30,000,000 to make it.
You take $29 and a half
million for yourself.
I get a lousy $800.
I don't get any credit.
And my movie's
released as a trailer?
(Crow cries out in frustration)
It's okay, it's okay, buddy.
Uh-huh, that's right.
Good, we're all
on the same page.
Now, I'm going to be at
Sundance on Wednesday.
I'll be in Paris on Friday,
and then Cannes on Saturday.
So don't try and
get a hold of me.
Becca, where are those tickets?
Becca?
Mother, I think I can
get my whole head in here.
That's nice, dear.
Becca, push the button.
Becca.
(sweeping music)
Let's get the hell outta here.
(plucky chase music)